http://www.expandingopportunities.org/privacy-policy/

Expanding Opportunities
Increasing self-sufficiency through educational and charitable projects for people nationally and internationally.
Our Blog
MenuHomeWhat We DoOur ProjectsThe NeedOur PartnersWays to HelpMake a DonationDonate ItemsWork for UsVolunteerShop Ex OpFAO TravelCobb WorkshopOn the BeachService JourneyTravel CircleAbout UsPublicationsAdministrationContact InfoOur Blog
Privacy PolicyYour Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
• See what data we have about you, if any.
• Change/correct any data we have about you.
• Have us delete any data we have about you.
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Registration
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-207-930-8012 USA or via email to info@expandingopportunities.org.
Search for:
Copyright © 2020 Expanding Opportunities. Proudly powered by WordPress. Silverclean design by Iceable Themes.
